<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>monitoring-observability on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/monitoring-observability/</link><description>Recent content in monitoring-observability on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/monitoring-observability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sentry</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/sentry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/sentry/</guid><description>Sentry helps developers ship better software faster by tracking errors and performance issues in real-time. When your application crashes or slows down, Sentry tells you exactly what went wrong, where it happened, and who was affected.
Key Features Real-time Error Tracking: Catch errors as they happen with full stack traces Performance Monitoring: Track slow transactions and identify bottlenecks Release Tracking: See which deployment introduced issues Smart Alerts: Get notified about critical errors, not noise User Impact: Know exactly how many users are affected Multi-platform: Supports 100+ languages and frameworks Why Teams Choose Sentry Sentry provides context that logs can&amp;rsquo;t - showing the exact line of code, user actions, and environment that led to each error.</description></item><item><title>Splunk</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/splunk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/splunk/</guid><description>Splunk turns machine data into insights. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s server logs, security events, or IoT sensors, Splunk ingests any data and makes it searchable, analyzable, and actionable at enterprise scale.
Used by 92 of the Fortune 100 companies, Splunk is the platform that IT operations, security teams, and business analysts rely on to understand what&amp;rsquo;s happening across their entire technology stack.
Key Features Universal Data Ingestion: Collect data from any source - logs, metrics, events, traces Powerful Search Language: Query terabytes of data in seconds with SPL (Search Processing Language) Real-time Monitoring: Set alerts and dashboards that respond to events as they happen Machine Learning: Built-in ML algorithms detect anomalies and predict issues Security Analytics: SIEM capabilities for threat detection and incident response Custom Dashboards: Create visualizations that tell your data&amp;rsquo;s story Why Teams Choose Splunk Splunk excels at finding needles in haystacks.</description></item><item><title>Zabbix</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/zabbix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/zabbix/</guid><description>Zabbix is the open-source enterprise monitoring solution trusted by organizations worldwide to keep their IT infrastructure running smoothly. It monitors everything from servers and networks to applications and services in real-time.
Used by companies like ING Bank, T-Mobile, and SoftBank, Zabbix handles monitoring at massive scale while remaining completely free and open-source. It&amp;rsquo;s the monitoring platform that grows with your infrastructure.
Key Features Auto-Discovery: Automatically detect and start monitoring new devices and services Real-time Monitoring: Collect and analyze metrics with sub-second precision Predictive Analytics: Identify potential issues before they become problems Flexible Alerting: Customizable notifications via email, SMS, Slack, and more Web Interface: Comprehensive dashboards and configuration through web UI Distributed Monitoring: Scale monitoring across multiple locations and data centers Why IT Teams Choose Zabbix Zabbix combines enterprise features with open-source flexibility.</description></item></channel></rss>