<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>version-control-collaboration on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/version-control-collaboration/</link><description>Recent content in version-control-collaboration on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/version-control-collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GitHub</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/github/</guid><description>GitHub is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest code hosting platform and the social network for developers, home to over 100 million repositories and 83 million developers.
More than just Git hosting, GitHub has become the central hub for open-source development, team collaboration, and modern DevOps workflows.
What makes GitHub essential:
Git hosting - Unlimited public and private repositories with full version control Pull requests - Industry-standard code review and collaboration workflow Issues &amp;amp; project management - Track bugs, features, and organize work GitHub Actions - Powerful CI/CD automation directly integrated with your code Core collaboration features:</description></item><item><title>GitLab</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/gitlab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/gitlab/</guid><description>GitLab is a comprehensive DevOps platform that integrates Git repository management, CI/CD pipelines, security scanning, and project management in a single application.
Key Features Complete DevOps platform - All development tools in one integrated solution Built-in CI/CD - Automated pipelines for testing, building, and deployment Security scanning - Integrated vulnerability and compliance testing Container registry - Built-in Docker image storage and management Issue tracking - Project management with boards and milestones Merge requests - Advanced code review with approval workflows Wiki and documentation - Built-in knowledge management Self-hosted options - Deploy on-premises or in the cloud Use Cases Complete DevOps transformation and implementation Organizations eliminating tool sprawl Teams requiring integrated CI/CD and security Self-hosted Git repository management Enterprise development with compliance needs Get Started with GitLab Implement complete DevOps with integrated development platform.</description></item></channel></rss>