<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deployment-hosting on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/deployment-hosting/</link><description>Recent content in deployment-hosting on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/deployment-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Heroku</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/heroku/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/heroku/</guid><description>Heroku is a cloud platform that enables developers to deploy, manage, and scale applications with Git-based workflows and zero server administration.
Key Features Git-based deployment - Deploy applications with simple git push Add-on ecosystem - Over 200 add-ons for databases, monitoring, caching Auto-scaling - Automatic application and database scaling Multi-language support - Ruby, Node.js, Python, Java, PHP, Go, Scala Review apps - Temporary apps for each pull request Pipeline management - Staging and production environments Dyno management - Containerized application processes CLI tools - Comprehensive command-line interface Use Cases Rapid prototyping and MVP development Web application deployment API and microservices hosting Team collaboration projects CI/CD pipeline integration Get Started with Heroku Deploy applications instantly with git push workflows.</description></item><item><title>Vercel</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/vercel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/vercel/</guid><description>Vercel is a frontend deployment platform optimized for Next.js and React applications with zero-configuration workflows and global edge distribution.
Key Features Next.js optimization - Built specifically for Next.js apps Edge functions - Serverless functions at the network edge Preview deployments - Every branch gets a URL Image optimization - Automatic image resizing and formats Global CDN - Fast content delivery worldwide Incremental static regeneration - Update static content dynamically Analytics - Core web vitals and performance metrics Team collaboration - Share previews and manage deployments Use Cases Next.</description></item></channel></rss>