<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>project-management-platforms on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/project-management-platforms/</link><description>Recent content in project-management-platforms on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/project-management-platforms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Airtable</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/airtable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/airtable/</guid><description>Airtable combines the simplicity of spreadsheets with the power of databases. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wished Excel could do more, or databases were less intimidating, Airtable is your answer.
Teams use Airtable to manage everything from content calendars to product roadmaps, customer CRMs to event planning. Its flexibility means you can start simple and scale up as your needs grow, without migrating to a new platform.
What Makes Airtable Different Visual Database: Link records between tables to create powerful relational databases Multiple Views: See your data as a grid, calendar, kanban board, or gallery Rich Field Types: Attachments, checkboxes, dropdowns, formulas, and more Automation: Set up triggers to automate repetitive tasks Templates: Start fast with pre-built bases for common use cases Key Features • Spreadsheet-database hybrid interface - Familiar spreadsheet view with powerful relational database capabilities underneath • Customizable field types - Rich data types including attachments, checkboxes, formulas, and linked records • Multiple view options - Grid, calendar, kanban, gallery, and form views for diverse data visualization needs • Automation and workflows - Trigger-based automation with conditional logic and cross-table operations • Collaboration and sharing - Real-time collaboration with granular permissions and external sharing capabilities • Extensive integration ecosystem - Native connections with popular business tools and robust API access • Template library - Pre-built solutions for common use cases across industries and departments • Mobile accessibility - Full-featured mobile apps with offline capability and real-time synchronization</description></item><item><title>LiquidPlanner</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/liquidplanner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/liquidplanner/</guid><description>LiquidPlanner is the project management tool that finally makes project schedules realistic. Instead of fixed deadlines that everyone knows are wrong, LiquidPlanner uses intelligent scheduling that adapts to reality - accounting for priorities, interruptions, and resource constraints.
Trusted by companies like Fitbit, Zynga, and Plantronics, LiquidPlanner solves the biggest problem in project management: schedules that break the moment something changes. Its priority-driven approach means projects get done in the right order, on time.</description></item><item><title>Project.co</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/project.co/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/project.co/</guid><description>Project.co is the project management platform that proves powerful doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to mean complicated. Built with a focus on exceptional user experience, it delivers enterprise-grade features through an interface your team will actually enjoy using.
While traditional PM tools often feel like administrative burden, Project.co transforms project management into a smooth, intuitive experience. Teams report higher adoption rates and better project outcomes thanks to its modern design and intelligent automation.</description></item><item><title>ProjectManager.com</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/projectmanager.com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/projectmanager.com/</guid><description>ProjectManager.com is the enterprise project management platform that brings order to organizational chaos. When you&amp;rsquo;re juggling multiple projects, teams, and stakeholders, this is the tool that keeps everything on track with real-time visibility and powerful oversight capabilities.
Built for serious project management, ProjectManager.com supports whatever methodology works for your team - Gantt charts for traditional planning, Kanban boards for agile workflows, or hybrid approaches that combine the best of both worlds.</description></item></channel></rss>