<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attendance-absence-management on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/attendance-absence-management/</link><description>Recent content in attendance-absence-management on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/attendance-absence-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Factorial</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/factorial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/factorial/</guid><description>Factorial is the all-in-one HR platform that helps growing businesses manage their entire employee lifecycle. From onboarding to performance reviews, time tracking to payroll, Factorial centralizes everything HR teams need in one intuitive platform.
Used by over 10,000 companies across Europe and Latin America, Factorial eliminates the need for multiple HR tools by providing a comprehensive solution that scales with your business.
Key Features Employee Management: Complete employee records with document storage Time Tracking: Clock in/out with mobile apps and automatic overtime calculation Leave Management: Request, approve, and track time off with policy automation Performance Reviews: 360-degree feedback and goal tracking Payroll Integration: Seamless connection with payroll providers HR Analytics: Workforce insights and reporting dashboards Perfect For Growing businesses (50-500 employees) outgrowing spreadsheets Companies wanting to consolidate multiple HR tools Teams needing better visibility into workforce metrics Organizations preparing for compliance requirements Why HR Teams Choose Factorial Factorial replaces 5-10 different HR tools with one platform.</description></item><item><title>LeaveBoard</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/leaveboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/leaveboard/</guid><description>LeaveBoard makes employee leave management simple and stress-free. No more spreadsheets, email chains, or confused managers - just a clean, modern platform that handles all your absence tracking automatically.
Built for growing teams who&amp;rsquo;ve outgrown basic vacation tracking, LeaveBoard brings professional HR capabilities without the enterprise complexity. Employees can request time off in seconds, managers approve with one click, and HR stays compliant effortlessly.
Why teams love LeaveBoard:
One-click approvals - Managers approve requests instantly from any device Smart notifications - Never miss a request or forget about upcoming absences Automatic calculations - Vacation balances update in real-time Team calendar - See who&amp;rsquo;s out at a glance Perfect for:</description></item></channel></rss>