<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>time-tracking-for-freelancers on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/time-tracking-for-freelancers/</link><description>Recent content in time-tracking-for-freelancers on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/time-tracking-for-freelancers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TopTracker</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/toptracker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/toptracker/</guid><description>TopTracker is the free time tracking app that helps freelancers build trust with clients through transparent work verification. With automatic screenshots and activity monitoring, it proves you&amp;rsquo;re working when you say you are.
Built by Upwork, TopTracker solves the biggest challenge in remote freelancing: proving productivity to clients. The app captures periodic screenshots and tracks activity levels, giving clients confidence in the hours you bill.
Key Features 100% Free: No limits, no subscriptions - completely free forever Screenshot Verification: Optional screenshots show clients what you&amp;rsquo;re working on Activity Tracking: Keyboard and mouse activity levels prove you&amp;rsquo;re actively working Time Tracking: Accurate time capture with project and task organization Client Sharing: Send transparent time reports directly to clients Privacy Controls: You control when screenshots are taken and what&amp;rsquo;s shared Perfect for Freelancers Who Need to prove productivity to skeptical clients Want transparent billing without disputes Work with clients who require verification Bill hourly and need detailed time records Why Freelancers Choose TopTracker TopTracker eliminates the &amp;ldquo;trust problem&amp;rdquo; in remote work.</description></item></channel></rss>