<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security-compliance-tools on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/security-compliance-tools/</link><description>Recent content in security-compliance-tools on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/security-compliance-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HashiCorp Vault</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/hashicorp-vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/hashicorp-vault/</guid><description>HashiCorp Vault secures, stores, and tightly controls access to tokens, passwords, certificates, and encryption keys. It&amp;rsquo;s the secrets management solution trusted by enterprises to protect their most sensitive data.
From startups to Fortune 500 companies, Vault eliminates secrets sprawl by centralizing all sensitive data in a single, secure location with fine-grained access controls and comprehensive audit trails.
Key Features Dynamic Secrets: Generate secrets on-demand with automatic expiration Data Encryption: Encrypt data at rest and in transit with key rotation Identity-Based Access: Fine-grained policies control who can access what Audit Logging: Complete audit trail of all secrets access and operations Multi-Cloud Ready: Works across AWS, Azure, GCP, and on-premises API First: Programmatic access for automation and integration Why Security Teams Choose Vault Vault eliminates the security risks of hardcoded passwords and scattered API keys.</description></item><item><title>Qualys</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/qualys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/qualys/</guid><description>Qualys is the cloud security platform that helps organizations identify, prioritize, and fix security vulnerabilities across their entire IT infrastructure. Trusted by over 19,000 customers worldwide, it&amp;rsquo;s the comprehensive solution for vulnerability management and compliance.
From Fortune 500 enterprises to government agencies, Qualys provides the continuous security monitoring and automated compliance reporting that keep organizations secure and audit-ready.
Key Features Continuous Scanning: Automated vulnerability detection across networks, web apps, and cloud assets Risk Prioritization: AI-powered scoring helps teams focus on the most critical threats Compliance Automation: Built-in frameworks for PCI DSS, SOX, HIPAA, and more Asset Discovery: Automatically discover and inventory all IT assets Threat Intelligence: Real-time threat data enhances vulnerability context Patch Management: Prioritize and track patch deployment across systems Why Security Teams Choose Qualys Qualys eliminates the complexity of managing multiple security tools by providing a unified cloud platform.</description></item></channel></rss>