<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>timesheet-management on ToolChest</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/tags/timesheet-management/</link><description>Recent content in timesheet-management on ToolChest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://toolchest.pro/tags/timesheet-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zoho People</title><link>https://toolchest.pro/categories/zoho-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://toolchest.pro/categories/zoho-people/</guid><description>Zoho People is the complete HR platform that includes powerful time tracking and timesheet management. Instead of juggling separate HR and time tracking tools, manage everything from employee records to project timesheets in one integrated system.
Used by over 30,000 companies worldwide, Zoho People connects time tracking with the full employee lifecycle - from onboarding to performance reviews. This integration provides better insights and eliminates data silos.
Key Features Integrated Timesheets: Time tracking that connects with employee records and projects Employee Self-Service: Workers can submit timesheets, request time off, and view pay stubs Approval Workflows: Automated routing of timesheets through managers and HR Project Time Tracking: Allocate time to specific projects and clients for billing HR Analytics: Reports that combine time data with employee performance metrics Mobile Apps: Track time and manage HR tasks from anywhere Perfect For Growing businesses (50-500 employees) outgrowing basic time tracking Companies wanting HR and time tracking in one platform Organizations needing project-based time allocation Teams requiring detailed timesheet approval workflows Why Companies Choose Zoho People Zoho People eliminates the need for separate HR and time tracking systems.</description></item></channel></rss>